So let me ask
you a question. Why
is it that some
people can get views
but really struggle to
generate sales from them
whilst others can make
a high ticket offer,
build a bang average
sales page, have no
sales call and just
email their list to
say sales are open
and everything just flies
off their shelf? Well,
I actually figured this
out for myself years
ago and it is
because of this part
of our pipe. This
is the secret sauce
to getting the biggest
and best results because
this section is where
you can warm people
up 10 times faster
than absolutely anywhere else
in our entire system.
And to do that,
you only do two
things. The first is
you make videos so
good people ask, how
is this even free?
And the second is
you make videos so
good people go, how
can I work with
this person? There is
no hack. There is
no trick to game
the system. For success
on both YouTube and
business, all you have
to do is make
the videos so flipping
good, your viewers start
to feel lucky that
they've discovered you. Now,
the bad news is
this is going to
require a really big
mindset shift for you
because most people want
to find the fast,
easy AI way to
knock out a quick
script that they can
just throw up. Most
people only spend an
hour or two writing
one. Most people rush.
Most people do not
want to do anything
I'm about to show
you because they're always
looking for the fast,
easy option. So all
we have to do
is not be like
most people who fail
at this game and
do the opposite and
work hard. Now, I
am here to help
you get faster at
this. We can save
time in so many
areas sticking to my
system. But this next
phase is not the
place to cut corners.
But also, it's the
hardest part because it's
going to require you
to really break yourself
to level up. You
are going to overthink.
You're going to go,
oh my gosh, this
takes me 10 times
longer than it used
to. You're going to
put all of this
effort into what I'm
showing you to do.
And it's going to
make no difference to
your viewers. You're going
to have to keep
going because you don't
just get good at
this after one video.
You practice it over
and over and over
again until it starts
to feel second nature.
And only after you've
posted 30, 40 or
50 videos doing this,
you're going to go,
oh my gosh, I'm
so glad I stuck
to that plan. It's
actually not as hard
as it was anymore.
So just don't be
like everyone else who's
looking for a shortcut
here. Apart from when
we launch a video,
this is one of
the highest stress points
in the process, but
also the most powerful.
And I know it
works. You're here because
of it. All right,
so what are we
going to break down
in this phase? The
three things that you
need to make a
video so good people
can't believe it's three.
Then we're going to
look at how to
write intros. After that,
we're going to go
deeper on video structure
and explore how to
make content so good
people go, how do
I work with this
person? We're then going
to look at storytelling,
metaphor, visual demos, frameworks,
ending a video, and
then how you optimize
your content for conversions,
as well as planning
a video. And then
writing one too. By
the end of this,
you are going to
have access to a
toolbox of techniques that
when practiced enough, will
turn your videos into
complete sales machines. And
all you need to
do is pick and
choose for them for
each video and get
good at knowing which
one to use where
and executing them over
the years. And please
just remember, we are
breaking you to be
remade into the Hulk
of a channel that
you want to be.
This is going to
be Max Payne. It's
also worth noting that
this phase is going
to take a lot
of time. If you
have to spend two
hours a day, two
to three weeks on
this and the tasks
that I give you
in it, then you
are moving at a
very fast rate. Don't
worry that you're falling
behind if things are
not instantly clicking or
if tasks feel hard.
This is very natural
with the position you're
in right now. All
right, let's move on
to check out the
basics of what makes
a flipping great script.